>> Brian Holt: 最后我想说的是 dev 工具，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Last thing I wanna
talk about here is dev tools,
这是绝对必要的
which are absolutely essential.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，我只邀请您去 google React dev 工具和
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So I would just invite
you to google React dev tools and
然后就放 Chrome 或 Firefox
then just put Chrome or Firefox.
我在火狐上很明显
I'm on Firefox, obviously, so.
>> Brian Holt: 此处显示 React Dev Tools ，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Here it
says React Dev Tools, and
我肯定有一个是谷歌 Chrome在那的
I'm sure there's one for,
Google Chrome's right there anyway.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 所以你来这里说我已经有了，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So you just come in
here and you say I already have them,
你就可以在这儿看到他们了对吧
you can see them right up here for
me, right?
但是 Chrome 也可以，你只需单击它，就可以在 Chrome上安装。
But Chrome as well, you just click that,
and you'll install that on Chrome.
>> Brian Holt: 我认为这是目前唯一存在的两个。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I think these
are the only two that exist right now.
边缘没有他们， Safari，我想他们已经摆脱他们了。
Edge doesn't have them, and Safari,
I think they got rid of them.
因此，您必须在 Firefox 或 Chrome 上使用它们。
So you either have to be on Firefox or
Chrome to have them.
新的边缘将会有它，它是由它来的。
The new Edge will have it,
the Edgium, as it were.
好，让我给你们演示一下如何使用它。
Okay, and let me show you
a little bit how to use this.
这是一个 " 雷法 " 应用程序。
So this is a React application.
您可以在上面看到它以开发者方式执行 React ，因为它处于红色状态。
You can see up there that it has React
in developer mode because it's in red.
>> Brian Holt: 然后我可以在这里打开我的开发工具，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
then I can open my dev tools here, and
我有一个新的 " 雷法 " 标签
I have a new React tab right there.
所以我要点击这个， >> Brian Holt: 现在我有了
So I'll click on that,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And now I have
一个 DOM 探索者，我可以探索一下我是否在探索一个 DOM 树，对吧 ?
a DOM explorer, and I can explore as
if I was exploring a DOM tree, right?
你可以看到那边的斯特里特方式一个应用
So you can see StrictMode there, an app,
然后我就能看到我的搜索参数了
then I can see my searchParams thing and
I can highlight it, right?
它将在页面上显示该组件。
And it will show me that
component on the page.
在里面我可以看到下拉菜单
Inside of that I can see the drop downs.
我有什么事要做吗
And what's cool is here,
do I have anything passing params around?
我不知道
I don't really.
但你可以在这里看到，你可以看到这里的一些道具。
But you can see here,
you can see some of the props here.
我能看到它所拥有的所有孩子
I can see all the children that it has,
it's
用于 React 应用程序的有用的 DOM 资源管理器，对吗 ?
a useful kind of DOM explorer for
a React application, right?
说我有个大应用程序要找滴，所以
Let's say I have a big application
I need to find drop down, so
我就能在这里输入
I can just type in here, drop down,
它也会在那里搜寻，这也很有用。
and it'll actually search for
drop down there, which is useful as well.
我可以在这里点击这件事，我可以弄清楚这件事是从哪里来的，
I can click this thing right here, and I
can figure out where this is coming from,
这样我就能找到这个输入然后点击这个
so I can find this input and
click on that.
就像，好吧，这是你要找的输入。
And it's like, okay,
this is the input you're looking for.
我能看到它所得到的属性改变处理程序
I can see the properties that
it's getting, the change handler,
占位符值等等。
the placeholder value,
and so on and so forth.
你可以做点别的事让我们说我只是在页面上
Something else cool you can do,
let's say I'm just on the page here and
我要在这里找到这个 " 提交 " 按钮。
I want to find this
Submit button right here.
所以你可以右键单击它
So you can right-click on it,
表示 " 检查元素" ，就像通常那样，对吗 ?
say Inspect Element,
just like you normally would, right?
这会带你去探长
This will take you to the inspector, but
如果我点击 React dev 工具，还会突出显示，对吧 ?
if I click on the React dev tools,
it will still be highlighted, right?
还有最后一件事我可以进入控制台
And then last thing here,
I can actually go into the console, and
如果我想搞砸我就能把它放了
if I wanna mess around with it,
I can put $R, and
在 React dev 工具中选择的任何内容都将在我的控制台中为 $R 。
whatever is selected in the React dev
tools will be $R inside of my console.
因此，我也可以通过编程方式来处理它。
So I can programmatically
manipulate it there as well.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特:
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And just so you know,
你也可以跟巡官那样做
you can actually do that
with the inspector as well.
所以如果我点击那我就放了零
So if I click on that and I put $0,
你也可以和普通的探长一样
you can do that with just
the normal inspector as well.
我认为你可以做 1 美元，这可能只是一个 Chrome 的事情，但是
And I think you can do $1,
that might be a Chrome-only thing, but
就能抓住你之前抓住的东西对吧
that'll grab the previous thing
that you have grabbed, right?
因此， dev 工具非常有助于执行 React 应用程序，
So the dev tools are very very
helpful in doing React applications,
一些你想确定的东西
something you wanna have installed for
sure.
>> 扬声器 2: 如果我们投票的是站点的生产版本，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: If we're voting
the production version of the site,
当我单击工具的图标时，会收到警告，
I get a warning when I click
on the icon for the tools,
警告说我们用的是生产带或发展带
warning that we're using the production
belt or the development belt.
是 " 雷法" 工具或开发带的发展带吗 ?
Is that the development belt of
the tools or development belt of React?
>> Brian Holt: 你在哪里看到的?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Where are you seeing that?
>> 演讲者 2: 在您的扩展中，单击该内容。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: In your extensions,
clicking on that.
>> Brian Holt: 对，是什么 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Right, so what's it?
如果我去 Netflix.com ， > Brian Holt: 这
If I go to Netflix.com,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: This
主页是使用 React 的生产构建构建的，对吗 ?
homepage is built using
the production build of React, right?
所以这只是让你知道
So it's just letting you know hey,
您处于开发方式，不应将其装运到生产环境。
you're in development mode, you should
not be shipping this to production.
在你的发展中环境下就可以了
It's okay to have in your developing
environment, as you should,
但这是你进入生产时应该看到的
but this is what you should see
when you go into production.
>> 扬声器 2: 不是 Parcel 转 iling 和 munifying 什么的，然后是什么
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Isn't Parcel transpiling and
munifying everything, and then what
我们在这里呈现，我们打开的是生产版本还是不?
we're rendering here, what we have
opened is the production version or no?
>> Brian Holt: 仍然是开发版本，这是您想要的，对吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: It's still the development
version, which is what you want, right?
库兹如果我没有开发环境
Cuz if I didn't have
the development environment,
那我就不会得到 React 给你的有用的错误信息了
then I wouldn't get all the useful
error messages that React has for you.
就说错了，祝你好运，对吧 ?
It would just say an error happened,
and good luck, right?
>> Brian Holt: 不是这样说的。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Instead of saying
this broke at this line in this way.
>> 演讲者 2: 好的，谢谢。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Okay, thank you.
所以即使我们把它从 dist 文件夹中跑出来，也不是生产。
So even though we're running it out of
the dist folder, it's not production.
>> Brian Holt: 对。 >> 演讲者 2: 好的。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Right.
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Okay.
>> Brian Holt: 是的，我将向您演示如何在稍后构建该产品。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Yeah, I'll show you
how to build it for production later.
>> 演讲者 2: 谢谢。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Thanks.